Previously on the show.
Episode sebelumnya.
The sheep thought Wolffy took
Para kambing berpikir Wolffy mengambil pensil warna hijau untuk membuat pelangi,
so they tailed him secretly.
jadi mereka membuntuti dia.
But they discovered that it was a misunderstanding.
Ternyata itu hanya salah paham.
It turned out that the green color pencil was in Paddi's backpack all along.
Ternyata pensil warna hijau ada di ransel Paddi.
So what will happen next?
Apa yang akan terjadi berikutnya.
"Flying Island: The Sky Adventure: Crisis of Doppelgangers."
Petualangan Langit Pulau Terbang: Krisis Doppelgänger
Paddi!
Paddi!
Where did Paddi go this early in the morning?
Ke mana Paddi pergi pagi-pagi begini?
The early bird gets the worms.
Bangun pagi akan dapat rezeki.
Paddi, you are abusing Magic Train again.
Paddi, kau salah gunakan Kereta Ajaib lagi.
Sorry, I won't do it again.
Maaf, takkan kuulangi.
It's our turn to clean today.
Kini giliran kita beres-beres.
Yes, I promise I will complete the task.
Ya, tugasku pasti selesai!
The current time is 12 noon...
Saat ini pukul 12.00...
Oh no! The limited sale of rainbow pudding has started.
Gawat! Penjualan puding pelangi terbatas sudah mulai.
Wait. Didn't you say we're doing the cleaning together?
Tunggu. Bukankah kau bilang kita bersih-bersih bersama?
I will use my doppelgangers to help you with the cleaning.
Nanti ada doppelgänger untuk bantu.
Oh no! I won't make it!
Tidak! Aku takkan berhasil!
Oh dear, it's Wolffy.
Astaga, itu Wolffy.
How about I buy you this car?
Bagaimana kalau Ayah belikan mobil ini?
You just bought me one yesterday.
Ayah baru saja membelikanku kemarin.
How about this one?
Kalau yang ini?
You bought me that the day before yesterday too.
Ayah membelikanku kemarin lusa.
Let's look at other toys.
Mari lihat mainan lain.
What other toys has Willie not played with before?
Mainan apa lagi yang tak Willie punya?
Oh, I can't think of anything.
Aku tak terpikirkan apa pun
I should leave before Wolffy finds out I'm here.
Harus pergi sebelum Wolffy tahu aku di sini.
No. I have to find a place to hide first.
Gawat. Harus cari tempat sembunyi.
This is strange. Where did that little spaceship go?
Aneh. Mana kapal luar angkasa kecil itu?
Dad, I want this spaceship.
Ayah, aku mau kapal luar angkasa ini.
Shop owner, I'll take this.
Aku beli ini.
Sure.
Tentu.
Great! Let's go home and play with the spaceship.
Hebat! Ayo pulang dan memainkannya.
How did this happen?
Kenapa bisa begini?
I can finally work on my invention.
Akhirnya bisa mengerjakan penemuanku.
Spaceship, go...
Kapal luar angkasa, jalan...
If I knew this would happen, I'd have cleaned with Weslie.
Jika tahu akan begini, aku akan menemani Weslie saja.
No. I must escape before Wolffy finds out.
Tidak. Aku harus kabur sebelum Wolffy tahu.
Great. The gate is open.
Bagus. Pintunya terbuka.
Wow! The spaceship is moving on its own again.
Wah! Kapal luar angkasa bergerak sendiri lagi.
This is strange. Did I get the recipe wrong?
Aneh. Apa bahan-bahanku salah?
I'm so close to escaping.
Aku hampir kabur.
Spaceship, why are you going around? Let's play together.
Kapal luar angkasa, kenapa berkeliling? Ayo bermain bersama.
How can I let Willie know I am here without letting Wolffy know?
Bagaimana bisa beri tahu Willie ada aku tanpa ketahuan Wolffy?
This is...
Ini...
It worked. Willie recognized me.
Berhasil. Willie mengenaliku.
Dad. Look. This spaceship can stack blocks on its own.
Ayah. Lihat. Kapal luar angkasa ini bisa menumpuk blok dengan sendirinya.
Oh no! I can't let Wolffy find out.
Tidak! Wolffy jangan sampai tahu!
Dad, look.
Ayah, lihat.
This is strange.
Ini aneh.
Willie, I'm really busy now. Go play on your own.
Willie, Ayah sedang sibuk. Bermainlah sendiri.
Phew!
Astaga!
This way, Willie will surely understand.
Dengan cara ini, Willie pasti akan mengerti.
Willie, look this way.
Willie, lihat sebelah sini.
What did Willie draw?
Apa yang digambar Willie?
Great! Wolffy left.
Hebat! Wolffy pergi.
Now I can tell Willie my identity openly.
Kini bisa beri tahu Willie identitasku.
Willie, look this way.
Willie, lihat ke sebelah sini.
Willie.
Willie.
I give up.
Aku menyerah.
Willie, come with me. We're going out.
Willie, ikut Ibu. Kita pergi.
Okay.
Baiklah.
-Let's go. -Okay.
- Ayo. - Baiklah.
Good timing.
Waktu yang tepat.
What was that sound?
Suara apa itu?
Wolffy almost found me again.
Wolffy hampir menemukanku lagi.
What should I do now? Right!
Aku harus bagaimana?
I didn't think they could help out with cleaning too.
Tak kuduga mereka bisa bantu beres-beres.
Paddi!
Paddi!
How come my doppelgangers are not here yet?
Kenapa doppelgängerku belum datang?
This is strange. Where did the screw go?
Ini aneh. Di mana sekrupnya?
Oh no! Wolffy is coming.
Gawat! Wolffy datang.
I still need a hammer and an apple.
Aku masih butuh palu dan apel.
I'm safe finally.
Akhirnya aku aman.
Thank you, Paddi.
Terima kasih, Paddi.
The goat I have wanted to catch is right by me after all.
Kambing yang mau kutangkap ternyata ada di dekatku.
You are not getting away this time.
Kini kau tak bisa lolos.
They're here at last.
Akhirnya mereka tiba.
Since you are here, let me give you a taste of my vacuum cleaner
Karena kau di sini, rasakan pengisap debuku
that is specially designed to
yang dirancang khusus untuk melawan doppelgänger Kereta Ajaib.
Wolffy, I'm afraid you'll be disappointed.
Wolffy, kurasa kau akan kecewa.
Magic Train, combine!
Kereta Ajaib, bersatu!
This was the worst combining mode I've seen.
Itu penyatuan terburuk yang pernah ada.
What's going on?
Ada apa?
How come I'm one cart short?
Kenapa kurang satu?
You're not going anywhere.
Kau takkan lolos.
Where did the last piece go?
Di mana yang terakhir?
What happened?
Apa yang terjadi?
Your invention is not that good either.
Penemuanmu juga tak sebagus itu.
How dare you laugh at my invention? I will show you!
Berani sekali mentertawakan penemuanku? Akan kutunjukkan padamu!
Is Wolffy crazy?
Apa Wolffy gila?
Whatever. I'll just run.
Terserah. Aku harus kabur.
I made it.
Aku berhasil.
This is my upgraded vacuum cleaner. You're not going anywhere!
Ini pengisap debu tercanggihku. Kau takan bisa lolos!
Dad!
Ayah!
Mom and I picked up a spaceship on the street
Ibu dan aku dapat kapal luar angkasa yang persis seperti dari toko mainan.
Willie is in there! Magic Train, Combine!
Willie ada di sana! Kereta Ajaib, bersatu!
Even if you are combined, my vacuum cleaner can suck you in.
Meski bersatu, pengisap debuku bisa menyedotmu.
Magic Train, full power.
Kereta Ajaib, kekuatan penuh.
Paddi, I'll get you!
Paddi, akan kutangkap kau!
Paddi, remember. Don't ever abuse Magic Train again.
Paddi, ingat. Jangan salah gunakan Kereta Ajaib lagi.
I won't.
Tidak akan.
Right, Weslie, I found something interesting.
Weslie, aku dapat sesuatu yang menarik.
Look.
Lihat.
Wolffy's vacuum cleaner is quite fun. It can be used for cleaning.
Pengisap debu Wolffy cukup seru. Bisa dipakai untuk beres-beres.
I think it's better not to use Wolffy's things.
Lebih baik tak pakai barang Wolffy.
Ouch! Weslie, please help me.
Aduh!
I told you not to use it.
Sudah kubilang jangan pakai itu.
I won't do it ever again.
Aku takkan mengulanginya.
TO BE CONTINUED 2762 DAYS FROM SETTING SAIL
BERSAMBUNG 2.762 HARI SEBELUM PULANG